Finding Aid for Jeffrey R. Parsons papers, 1960-2013
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Archaeological Sites and Projects 1966-2010
  - Peru 1996-2010
    - Junin Survey
      - Jun-?-40(TK) Unit 35-TK Junin 1976 30880-NW Site 183-184 Small Inca Tambo (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-41(TK) Fea 31-TK Junin 1976 30880-NW (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-42(TK) Fea 32-TK Junin 1976 30875-SE Site 57-58 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-43(TK) Fea 33-TK Junin 1976 30880-NW Site 182 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-44(TK) Fea 34-TK Junin 1976 30880-NW Site 185 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LH-1(R) no field no. Junin 1976 30880-SW Tambo Tilarnioj (Box 51)
      - Junin-1976 General Photos -- Parsons (Box 51)
      - Illustrations -- Upper Mantaro Survey (Box 51)
      - Hastings Survey Area Maps (Box 51)
      - Photos -- Suggestions for Illustrations in Final Monograph (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-1(H) Unit 76-H (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-2(H) Unit 77-H "Purumarca" (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-3(H) Unit 79-H "Rinripata" 34 (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-4(H) Unit 81-H "Huanchan" 76 (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-5(H) Unit 82-H "Ayajirco" 33 (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-6(H) Unit 83-H 32 (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-7(H) Unit 84, 85-H Coll 113,114-H Chupas and Hu-?-30 101 (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-8(H) Unit 86-H 100 (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-9(H) Coll 115-H 77 (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-10(H) Unit 87-H 79 (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-11(H) Unit 89-H 81 (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-12(H) Unit 90-H 31 "Paugarmarca" (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-13(H) Unit 93-H; Coll 116-118-H 37 "Carita" (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-14(H) Unit 94-H 67 (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-15(H) Unit 97-H (Box 51)
      - Hu-Li-16(H) Coll 120-H (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-17(H) Unit 98-H 48 (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-18(H) Unit 100-H 40 (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-19(H) Unit 101-H 39 "Pirhuayoc" (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-20(H) Unit 102-H 49 "Huaychomarca" (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-21(H) Unit 104-H 51 "Jachapata" (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-22(H) Coll 121-H "Cotosh" (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-23(H) Coll 122-H 29 "Okshacoto" (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-24(H) Unit 111-H 28 (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-25(H) Unit 112-H 27 "Pucusmarca" (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-26(H) Unit 114-H 23 "Huaychamarca" (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-27(H) Unit 115-H 22 (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-28(H) Unit 119-H 54 (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-29(H) Units 123,124-H 16 "Paraupunta" (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-30(H) Unit 126-H 6 "Puyhuanloma" (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-31(H) Unit 127-H 9 "Chuquisyunca" (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-32(H) Unit 128-H 10 "Tingo" (Box 51)
      - Hu-LI-33(H) Unit 130-H 11 "Gaparina" (Box 51)
      - Hu-EI-1(H) Coll 112-H 71 (Box 51)
      - Hu-EI-2(H) Coll 119-H 103 "Chaquienloma" (Box 51)
      - Hu-EI-3(H) Coll123-H 36 (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-1(H) Unit 78-H 70 (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-2(H) Unit 80 35 (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-3(H) Fea 26,27 78 "Chiras" (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-4(H) Unit 88-H 80 (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-5(H) Unit 91-H 69 (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-6(H) Unit 92-H 68 (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-7(H) Fea 28-H 104 (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-8(H) Unit 95,96-H 44 "Purunmarca" and Hu-?-31(H) (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-9(H) Fea 29-H 47 (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-10(H) Fea 30 46 (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-11(H) Unit 99-H 42 (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-12(H) Fea 31-H 39 (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-13(H) Unit 103-H 52 "Torreocpunta" (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-14(H) Unit 105-H 50 (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-15(H) Unit 106-H 19 "Palmamonte" (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-16(H) Unit 107-H 53 (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-17(H) Unit 108-H 18 "Tranca" (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-18(H) Unit 109-H 17 H4 (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-19(H) Unit 110; Coll 124, 125-H 25 "Pucara" (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-20(H) Unit 113-H 24 (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-21(H) Unit 116-H 26 (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-22(H) Unit 117-H 21 (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-23(H) Unit 118-H 20 (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-24(H) Unit 120-H 14 "Ututo" (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-25(H) Unit 121-H 13 (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-26(H) Unit 122-H 7 (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-27(H) Unit 125-H 5 (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-28(H) Fea 32-H 8 (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-29(H) Unit 129-H 12 "Piruruhuay" (Box 51)
      - Hu-?-30(H) See Hu-LI-7(H) folder (Box 51)
      - Ta-LF-1(H) 39751 SE Tarma 1975 Fea 12H (Box 51)
      - Ta-EI-1(W) 2750 SW Tarma 1975 Coll 4W 289 (Box 51)
      - Ta-EI-2(W) 39751-NW, 16905 NE Tarma 1975 Unit 5W Coll 6W 7W 271 (Box 51)
      - Ta-EI-3(H) 2807 NW Tarma 1975 Coll 22H 23H 88 (Box 51)
      - Ta-EI-4(H) 2807 NE Tarma 1975 72 (Box 51)
      - Ta-EI-5(H) 2750 NE Tarma 1975 Unit 26H Coll 28H, 29H 288 (Box 51)
      - Ta-EI-6(H) 18823 NW Tarma 1975 Unit 27H 285 (Box 51)
      - Ta-EI-7(H) 18825 NE 2884 SE Tarma 1975 Unit 29H 373 (Box 51)
      - Ta-EI8(H) 2878 NW Tarma 1975 Coll 31H 274 (Box 51)
      - Ta-EI-9(H) 16907 SW Tarma 1975 Unit 31H 276 (Box 51)
      - Ta-EI-10(H) 1152 NE, 1156 SE Tarma 1975 Unit 38H 372 (Box 51)
      - Ta-EI-11(H) 2884 SW Tarma 1975 Unit 39H 371 (Box 51)
      - Ta-EI-12(H) 16907 SW Tarma 1975 Coll 39H 279 (Box 51)
      - Ta-EI-13(H) 16907 SW Tarma 1975 Unit 40 H Site 277 (Box 51)
      - Ta-EI-14(H) 2880 SE Tarma 1975 Coll 40H 41H 282 (Box 51)
      - Ta-EI-15(H) 16911-SW Tarma 1975 Unit 53 H 363 (Box 51)
      - Ta-EI-16(H) Unit 2-W (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-1(W) 2750 SW Tarma 1975 Unit 1W 287 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-2(W) 18821 SE Tarma 1975 Unit 2W 286 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-3(W) 2752 NE Tarma 1975 Unit 3W 270 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-4(W) 2752 SW Tarma 1975 Unit 4W 269 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-5(W) 2753 NE Tarma 1975 Coll 5W 264 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-6(W) 39751 SW Tarma 1975 Fea 9W 272 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-7(W) 39751 NW Tarma 1975 Fea 10W 259 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-8(W) 39751 NE Tarma 1975 Unit 6W Coll 8W 9W 260 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-9(W) 39751 NE Tarma 1975 Coll 10W 11W Fea 11W 252-253 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-10(W) 39751 NE Tarma 1975 Unit 7W 261 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-11(W) 39751 NE Tarma 1975 Coll 12 W 262 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-12(W) 39753 SE Tarma 1975 Coll 13W 91 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-13(W) 17015 C Tarma 1975 Unit 8W 73 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-14(H) 39751 SE Tarma 1975 Coll 14H 256 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-15(H) 39751 SE Tarma 1975 Unit 9H 257 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-16(H) 39751 SE Tarma 1975 Coll15H 255 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-17(H) 39751 SE Tarma 1975 Unit 10H Coll 16H 17H 254 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-18(H) 39751 SW Tarma 1975 Coll 19H 266 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-19(H) 39751 SW Tarma 1975 Coll 20H 267 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-20(H) 39751 C Tarma 1975 Unit 11H 265 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-21(H) 2807 NE Tarma 1975 Unit 12H 89 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-22(H) 2807 NW Tarma 1975 Coll 24H 90 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-23(H) 39751 C Tarma 1975 Coll 18H 263 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-24(H) 17015 NW Tarma 1975 Unit 14H 87 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-25 (H) 2801 NW Tarma 1975 Coll 25H 124 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-26(H) 2801 C Tarma 1975 Unit 17H Coll 26H 27H 129 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-27(H) 2799 NE Tarma 1975 Unit 18H 123 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-28(H) 2797 NE Tarma 1975 Unit 19H 105 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-29(H) 2797 NE Tarma 1975 Fea 13H 108 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-30(H) 2797 NW Tarma 1975 Unit 21 H 110 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-31 (H) 39755 SW Tarma 1975 Unit 23H 128 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-32(H) 39755 SW Tarma 1975 Unit 24 H 127 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-33(H) 16901 C Tarma 1975 Unit 25H 113 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-34(H) 2884 SE Tarma 1975 Unit 30H 369 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-35(H) 5215-76-SW Tarma 1975 Unit 32 H 142 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-36 (H) 5215-76-C Tarma 1975 Unit 33H 140 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-37(H) 5215-76-NW Tarma 1975 Unit 34 H 139 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-38(H) 5215-76-SW Tarma 1975 Coll 32 H 143 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-39(H) 2878 NE Tarma 1975 Unit 35H Coll 33H 34H 273 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-40(H) 5215-76-SW Tarma 1975 (not described in field) 141 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-41(H) 16911 NE Tarma 1975 Unit 44H Fea 16H, 17H 355 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-42(H) 16911-NW Tarma 1975 Coll 43H 359 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-43(H) 16911-NW Tarma 1975 Unit 47H 358 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-44(H) 16911 NW Tarma 1975 Unit 48H 356 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-45(H) 16911 SE Tarma 1975 Unit 49H, 50H Fea 20H 364, 365, 366-A (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-46(H) 16911 SE Tarma 1975 Coll 44H Fea 21H 366 (Box 51)
      - Ta-LI-47(H) 16911 NW Tarma 1975 Coll 45 H 360 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-48(H) 16903-NW Tarma 1975 Unit 22-H 126 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-49(H) 18823 SW Tarma 1975 Unit 28-H 284 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-50(H) 2882 NE Tarma 1975 Coll 30H 281 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-51(H) see Ta-LI-45 Tarma 1975 Unit 50-H Airphoto:16911 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-52(H) see Ta-LI-45(H) see Ta-LI-41(H) 16911 Tarma 1975 Unit 43-H 352 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LH-1(H) 2880 NW Tarma 1975 Uit 36H, 37H Coll 35H, 36H, 37H, 38H Tarma-Tambo 283 (Box 52)
      - Ta-Col-1(H) 17015 C Tarma 1975 Coll21H 251 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-1(W) 2752 NW Tarma 1975 Fea 8W 268 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-2(H) 17015 Tarma 1975 Unit 13H 86 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-3(H) Unit 16H 39755NE Tarma 1975 99 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-4(H) 2797 NW Tarma 1975 Fea 14H 106 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-5(H) 2797 NW Tarma 1975 Fea 15H 107 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-6(H) 2797 NW Tarma 1975 Unit 20H 109 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-7(H) 1031 NW Tarma 1975 Coll 42H 346 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-8(H) 1035 SW Tarma 1975 Unit 41H 275 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-9(H) 1031 SW Tarma 1975 Unit 42H 351 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-10(H) 1031 SW Tarma 1975 Fea 18H 350 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-11(H) 16911 SW Tarma 1975 Fea 19H 368 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-12(H) 16911 C Tarma 1975 Unit 51H 362 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-13(H) 16911 SW Tarma 1975 Unit 52H 361 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-14(H) 16911 SW Tarma 1975 Fea 22H 367 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-15(H) 16911 Tarma 1975 Fea 20-H 366-A (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-16(H) 16911 Tarma 1975 Unit 45-H 357 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-17(H) 16911 Tarma 1975 Fea 16-H 354 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-18(H) 16911 Tarma 1975 Fea 17-H 353 (Box 52)
      - Ta-EH-1(P) 2805 NE Tarma 1975 Coll 28P 85 (Box 52)
      - Ta-EI-1(P) 2908 NW Tarma 1975 Coll 10P, 11P Fea 5P 133 (Box 52)
      - Ta-EI-2(P) 16903 NW Tarma 1975 Unit 8P 135 (Box 52)
      - Ta-EI-3(P) 18819 Tarma 1975 Coll 18P 158 (Box 52)
      - Ta-EI-4(P) 2912 Tarma 1975 Coll19P 258 (Box 52)
      - Ta-EI-5(P) 2803 Tarma 1975 Coll 32P, 33P 95 (Box 52)
      - Ta-EI-6(P) 2803 SW Tarma 1975 Coll 34P 97 (Box 52)
      - Ta-EI-7(P) 2799 SW Tarma 1975 Unit 27P 114 (Box 52)
      - Ta-EI-8(P) 2799 SW Tarma 1975 Unit 28P 121 (Box 52)
      - Ta-EI-9(P) 5215-78-SE Tarma 1975 Unit 48P Coll 56, 48P 151 (Box 52)
      - Ta-EI-10(P) 18825-NW Tarma 1975 Unit 50-P 370 (Box 52)
      - Ta-EI-11(P) 16909 NW Tarma 1975 Unit 52 P 278 (Box 52)
      - Ta-EI-12(P) 16909 NW Tarma 1975 Unit 53P 374 (Box 52)
      - Ta-EI-13(P) 16909 NW Tarma 1975 Unit 54P 280 (Box 52)
      - Ta-EI-14(P) 16909 SE Tarma 1975 Unit 59P 349 (Box 52)
      - Ta-EI-15(P) 18819-NW Tarma 1975 Coll 14-P 164 (Box 52)
      - Ta-EI-16(P) 2799-SW Tarma 1975 Coll 37P 38P 125 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-1(P) 2748 SW 2746 NE Tarma 1975 Coll 1P, 2P, 3P Fea 1P 290 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-2(P) 2746 SW Tarma 1975 Unit 2P 299 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-3(P) 18821-NE Tarma 1975 Unit 1P 292 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-4(P) 2904 NW Tarma 1975 Unit 3P Coll6, 7, 8P 132 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-5(P) 2904 16903 Tarma 1975 Unit 4P 131 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-6(P) 16903 NE Tarma 1975 Unit 5P Yanamarca 130 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-7(P) 39753 Tarma 1975 Unit 7P 92 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-8(P) 18821 NW Tarma 1975 Coll 9P Fea 4P 292-A (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-9(P) 2910 NW Tarma 1975 Unit 9P 136 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-10(P) 18819 SW Tarma 1975 Unit 10P 161 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-11(P) 18819 SW Tarma 1975 Unit 11P 160 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-12(P) 18819 NW Tarma 1975 Unit 12P Coll 12,13,14P 164 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-13(P) 18819 NW Tarma 1975 Unit 13P 163 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-14(P) 18821 NE Tarma 1975 Unit 14P 291 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-15(P) 18821 NE Tarma 1975 Unit 15P 296 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-16(P) 18821 NE Tarma 1975 Unit 16P 294 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-17(P) 25377 SE Tarma 1975 Unit 17P 298 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-18(P) 18819 NE Tarma 1975 Unit 18P 155 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-19(P) 18819 Tarma 1975 Unit 19P 156 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-20(P) 18819 Tarma 1975 Coll15P 295 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-21(P) 2912 Tarma 1975 Coll24P 85 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-22(P) 39753 17013 SE Tarma 1975 Unit 20P 83 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-23(P) 2805 Tarma 1975 Unit 21P 84 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-24(P) 2805 NE Tarma 1975 Coll 25P, 26P 85 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-25(P) 2805 SW Tarma 1975 Unit 22P Coll 29, 30P 93 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-26(P) 2805 SW Tarma 1975 Coll 31P 94 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-27(P) 17013 Tarma 1975 Unit 23P (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-28(P) 17013 NW Tarma 1975 Unit 24P 98 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-29(P) 2799 SE Tarma 1975 Unit 26P 125 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-30(P) 2795 SE Tarma 1975 Unit 29P Coll 39P, 40P 112 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-31(P) 2799 NE Tarma 1975 Unit 30P 120 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-32(P) 2799 NE Tarma 1975 Unit 31P 116 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-33(P) 2799 NW Tarma 1975 Unit 32P 115 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-34(P) 2795 SE Tarma 1975 Unit 33P Coll 41P, 42P 111 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-35P 16901 NW Tarma 1975 Unit 34P Coll 43, 44P 152 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-36(P) 16901 NW Tarma 1975 Unit 35P 153 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-37(P) 18817 SE Tarma 1975 Unit 36P 154 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-38(P) 25379 SE Tarma 1975 Unit 38P 168 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-39(P) 25377 NE Tarma 1975 Unit 39P 157 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-40(P) 18817 SW Tarma 1975 Unit 40P 169 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-41(P) 25377 NE Tarma 1975 Unit 42P 162 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-42(P) 5215-78 SE Tarma 1975 Unit 43P 150 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-43(P) 5215-78 SE Tarma 1975 Unit 44P 147 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-44(P) 5215-78 SE Tarma 1975 Unit 45P 148 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-45(P) 5215-78 SE Tarma 1975 Unit 46P 145 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-46(P) 5215-78 NE Tarma 1975 Unit 47P 144 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-47(P) 5215-78 SE Tarma 1975 Unit 49P 149 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-48(P) 5215-78 NE Tarma 1975 Coll 45P 146 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-49(P) 16909 SW Tarma 1975 Unit 51P 348 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-50(P) 18827 NE Tarma 1975 Unit 56P 378 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-51(P) 18827 NE Tarma 1975 Unit 57P 379 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-52(P) 16909 Tarma 1975 Unit 60P 347 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LI-53(P) 18827 SW Tarma 1975 Unit 61P 381 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-1(P) 18821 NE Tarma 1975 Unit 6P 293 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-2(P) 2908 NW Tarma 1975 Fea 6P 134 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-3(P) 2803 NW Tarma 1975 Fea 7P 96 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-4(P) 2799 NW Tarma 1975 Fea 8P 119 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-5(P) 2799 NW Tarma 1975 Fea 9P 118 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-6(P) 2799 NW Tarma 1975 Fea 10P 122 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-7(P) 2799 NW Tarma 1975 Fea 11P 117 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-8(P) 18817 SW Tarma 1975 Unit 37P 170 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-9(P) 25377 SE Tarma 1975 Unit 41P 300 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-10(P) 16909 SW Tarma 1975 Coll 50P 376 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-11(P) 18827 SE Tarma 1975 Unit 58P (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-12(P) 18827 NE Tarma 1975 Fea 12P 380 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-13(P) 18827 NE Tarma 1975 Fea 13P 377 (Box 52)
      - Ta-?-14(P) 16909 SE Tarma 1975 Loc 3P (Box 52)
      - Ta-LH-1(P) 2912 Tarma 1975 Coll 16, 17, 21, 22, 23P Leticia 137 -- 159 (Box 52)
      - Ta-LH-2(P) 16909 SW Tarma 1975 Coll 49P 375 (Box 52)
      - Ta-Col-1(P) 2803 NE Tarma 1975 Unit 25P (Box 52)
      - Ta-Col-2(P) 16909 SW Tarma 1975 Unit 55P (Box 52)
    - Wanka Survey
      - Documentation 1975-1976 (Box 52)
      - Documentation 2002 (Box 52)
      - Maps -- Jauja, Huanca & Junin (Box 52)
      - Tarma 1975 Site-Unit-Fea-Coll J. Parsons (Box 52)
      - Jauja 1975 Site-Unit-Coll-Fea-Indices C. Hastings (Box 52)
      - Jauja 1975 Unit-Coll-Feat J. Parsons (Box 52)
      - Jauja 1975 Indices Parsons (Box 53)
      - Jauja 1975 Indices Hastings (Box 53)
      - Jauja 1976 Indices Parsons (Box 53)
      - Jauja 1976 Indices Parsons (Box 53)
      - Final Site Areas 1975-1976 (Box 53)
      - Final Site Areas Ta-Jau-Hu-Jun Site Area & Chronology -- Final Measures 1975-1976 (Box 53)
      - Jauja 1975 Site Tracings from Air Photos -- All Scales (Box 53)
      - Jauja 1976 Site Tracings (Box 53)
      - Tarma -- Jauja 1975 Coding Miscellaneous (Box 53)
      - Jauja 1975 Site Reports -- Final Hastings (Box 53)
      - Jauja 1976 Misc, General & Unknown Photos (Box 53)
      - Huacjlas -- Jauja (Box 53)
      - Ceramic Analysis 1975 Mantaro (Box 53)
      - Ceramic Analysis 1976 (Box 53)
      - leBlanc, Cathy UMARP-UMMA Site Correlations (Box 53)
      - Site Index for 1:25000 maps (Box 53)
      - Small Scale Maps with Schematic Site Symbols (Box 53)
      - INC Informe-maps (final copies) (Box 53)
      - Wanka -- Final Site Maps -- reduced size (Box 53)
      - Topo Map Indices (Box 53)
      - Airphoto Scale Computations & Airphoto Indices (Box 53)
      - Satellite Photos (Box 53)
      - Meteorological data 1960-1975 (Box 53)
      - Jauja Photo Record 1975, 2006 (Box 53)
      - Junin Lab photos 2010 (Box 53)
      - Jauja 1976 Jau-LI-70(P) Chawin -- 5X Blow up (Box 53)
      - Notes for BPM-2 (Box 53)
      - Survey Area Maps & lab work notes (Box 53)
      - Sherd drawings Huacrapulico EIP/MH (Box 53)
      - Sherd drawings -- Kim (Box 53)
      - Sherd Profiles & Drawings (Box 53)
      - Inka -- LH Sherd drawings (Box 53)
      - 1976 Color Sherds (Box 53)
      - Coleccion Sierra Central -- Veronica Castro 2006 (Box 53)
      - Junin Ceramic Inventory 2004 (Box 53)
      - Junin Ceramic Inventory 2008-2009 (Box 53)
      - Lima 206 -- Ceramics-Photo Records (Box 53)
      - Peru -- COARPE rules 2005-2006 (Box 53)
      - Jau-EH 1(H) 4430 B NE Jauja 1975 Coll 111-H(1975) Coll 152-P (1976) 509 (Box 53)
      - Jau-EI-1(H) 4420 C SW Jauja 1975 Coll 46H 423 (Box 53)
      - Jau-EI-2(H) 4420 C NW Jauja 1975 Coll 48H 420 (Box 53)
      - Jau-EI-3(H) 16915 SW Jauja 1975 Coll 50H, 266P 417 (Box 53)
      - Jau-EI-4(H) 4314 SE Jauja 1975 Coll 53H 437 (Box 53)
      - Jau-EI-4(H) 4314 SE Jauja 1975 Coll 53 H 437 (Box 53)
      - Jau-EI-5(H) 4314 A SE Jauja 1975 Coll 54H 438 (Box 53)
      - Jau-EI-6(H) 4312 B NW Jauja 1975 Unit 58H 444 (Box 53)
      - Jau-EI-7(H) 4296 D NE Jauja 1975 Coll 55H 436 (Box 53)
      - Jau-EI-8(H) Coll 56H 439 (Box 53)
      - Jau-EI-9(H) 4312 BSW Jauja 1975 Unit 59H Coll57H, 58H 442 (Box 53)
      - Jau-EI-10(H) 4298 D SE Jauja 1975 Coll 60H, 61H 440 (Box 53)
      - Jau-EI-11(H) 4312 A SW Jauja 1975 (Box 53)
      - Jau-EI-11(CH) 4312 A SW Jauja 1975 Coll 62H 445A (Box 53)
      - Jau-EI-12(H) 4298 C SW Jauja 1975 Unit 60H Coll 63-68H 464 (Box 53)
      - Jau-EI-13(H) 4298 B SW Jauja 1975 Unit 61H Coll 69H, 70H 469 (Box 53)
      - Jau-EI-14(H) 4658 C NE Jauja 1975 Coll 71H 470 (Box 53)
      - Jau-EI-15(H) 4318 A SE Jauja 1975 Unit 64H Coll 75 -- 79H 606 (Box 53)
      - Jau-EI-17(H) 4430 D SE Jauja 1975 Coll 110H 510 (Box 53)
      - Jau-LI-1(H) 4420 C SW, 4420 D NW Jauja 1975 Coll 49H 424 (Box 53)
      - Jau-LI-2(H) 16915 SE Jauja 1975 Unit 54H, Coll 264-P 416 (Box 53)
      - Jau-EI-16(H) 4426-C NE 4426 C SE Jauja 1975 Coll 100-103H 398 (Box 53)
      - Jau-LI-3(H) 4312 SE Jauja 1975 Coll 59H 441 (Box 53)
      - Jau-LI-4(H) 18833 NW 4300 B NE Jauja 1975 Unit 62H Coll 275P, 276P Jau-LI-6(P) 465 (Box 53)
      - Jau-LI-5(H) 4658 A SW Jauja 1975 Unit 63H Coll 72 -- 74H Fea 23H 476 (Box 53)
      - Jau-LI-6(H) 4288 A NW Jauja 1975 Coll 81H 557 (Box 53)
      - Jau-LI-7(H) 4288 A SE, 4288 C SW Jauja 1975 Unit 65H Coll 82, 83H 559 (Box 53)
      - Jau-LI-8(H) 4288-A SE, 4288 B NE Jauja 1975 Unit 66H Coll 84 -- 87H 564 (Box 53)
      - Jau-LI-9(H) 4288 A NW Jauja 1975 Unit 67H Coll 88, 89H Fea 24H 560 (Box 53)
      - Jau-LI-10(H) 4288 A SE Jauja 1975 Unit 68H 561 (Box 53)
      - Jau-LI-11(H) 4288 A SE Jauja 1975 Unit 69H Colcas 562 (Box 53)
      - Jau-LI-12(H) 4284 D SE Coll 90, 91H Coll 221P 574 (Box 53)
      - Jau-LI-13(H) Jauja 1975 (Box 53)
      - Jau-LI-14(H) 4284 D SE Jauja 1975 Unit 73, 75H Coll 92 -- 99H Coll 220P 572 (Box 53)
      - Jau-LI-15(H) 4426 B NE Jauja 1975 Coll 104 -- 107H 498 (Box 53)
      - Jau-LI-16 (H) 4426 B NW Jauja 1975 Coll 108H 497 (Box 53)
      - Jau-LH-1(H) 4322 ANW 4290 D NE Jauja 1975 Coll 80H Lump with Jau-LH-7(P) 551 (Box 53)
      - Jau-LH-2(H) 4284 D SW Jauja 1975 Unit 71H Colcas 577 (Box 54)
      - Jau-LH-3(H) 4284 D SW Jauja 1975 Unit 72H 576 (Box 54)
      - Jau-LH-4(H) 4284 D SE Jauja 1975 Unit 74H 573 (Box 54)
      - Jau-?-1(H) 4420C SW Jauja 1975 Coll 47H 419 (Box 54)
      - Jau-?-2(H) 16915 SW Jauja 1975 Unit 55H Coll 51, 52H Unit 118,119P 422 See Jau-?-33P (Box 54)
      - Jau-?-3(H) 4314 A NW Jauja 1975 Unit 56H 443 (Box 54)
      - Jau-?-4(H) 4312 A SW Jauja 1975 Unit 57H 445-B (Box 54)
      - Jau-?-5(H) 4288 A NW 4288 B SE Jauja 1975 Unit 70H Colcas 563 (Box 54)
      - Jau-?-6(H) 4284 B NE Jauja 1975 Fea 25H 578 (Box 54)
      - Jau-?-7(H) 4430 D NE Jauja 1975 Coll 109 H 507 (Box 54)
      - Jau-?-8(H) 4430 D NW Loc 1 H 506 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EH-1(P) 4278 A SE Jauja 1976 Coll 237P 623 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-1(P) 4422 A NE Jauja 1975 Unit 62P Coll 51P 477 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-2(P) 4294 D NW Jauja 1975 Coll 67P 603 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-3(P) 4294 D NW Jauja 1975 Coll 68P (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-4(P) 4294 D NW Jauja 1975 Coll 70P (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-5(P) 4294 D NE Jauja 1975 Coll 71P (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-6(P) 4294 C SW Jauja 1975 Coll 72, 76, 77P 435 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-7(P) 4294 C SW Jauja 1975 Coll 74P 433 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-8(P) 4294 C SW Jauja 1975 Coll 75P 434 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-9(P) 4294 C SE Jauja 1975 Coll 73P 432 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-10(P) 4296 B NE Coll 89P 474 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-11(P) 4654 C SE Coll 81P 593 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-12(P) 4294 A SW Jauja 1975 Coll 84P 592 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-13(P) 4654 D NE Jauja 1975 Coll 86P 598 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-14(P) 4296 B NW Jauja 1975 Coll 87P, 88P 473 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-15(P) 4294 B NW Jauja 1975 Unit 70P Coll 78P 600 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-18(P) 4294 B NE Jauja 1975 Coll 79P 604 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-17(P) 4294 B NW Jauja 1975 Unit 71P 599 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-19(P) 4656 D NW Jauja 1975 Coll 100P, 101P 595 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-19 (P) 4656 C SW Jauja 1975 Coll 102P, 103P 594 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-20(P) 4658 D NE Jauja 1975 Coll 104P 471 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-22(P) 4292 C SE Jauja 1975 Coll 110P 608 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-23 (P) 4292 D NE Jauja 1975 Coll 111P 609 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-21(P) 4292 D NE Jauja 1975 Coll 108P, 109P 610 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-24 (P) 4286 D NW + NE Jauja 1975 Coll 130P, 131P 569 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-25(P) 4284 C SE Jauja 1975 Unit 94P 371 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-26(P) 4424 D-NE Jauja 1975 Coll 141P 391 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-27(P) 4424 D SW Jauja 1975 Coll 142P 397 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-28(P) 4430 A SE Jauja 1975 Coll 149P 508 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-29(P) 4656 C NE Jauja 1975 Coll 90P 472 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-30(P) 4432 D SW Jauja 1976 Coll 153P/ 154P 522 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-31(P) 4432 C SW Jauja 1976 Coll 155P, 156P 511 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-32(P) 4752 C SE Jauja 1976 Coll 162P 518 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-33(P) 4752 B NE Jauja 1976 Coll 163P 520 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-34(P) 4752 B NE Jauja 1976 Coll 164P 521 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-35(P) 4752 B SE Jauja 1976 Coll 165P 524 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-36(P) 4752 C SW 4752 D NW Jauja 1976 Coll 167P, 168P 519 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-37(P) Coll 171P, 172P 526 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-38(P) 4754 B NE Jauja 1976 Coll 174P, 175P, 176P 533 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-39(P) 4754 B NE Jauja 1976 Coll 177P (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-40(P) 4754 D NW Jauja 1976 Coll 178P 531 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-41(P) 4754 D NW Jauja 1976 Coll 179P 530 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-42(P) 4434 B NE Jauja 1976 Coll 181P 527 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-43(P) 4436 B SE Jauja 1976 Coll 182P 541 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-44(P) 4438 A SE Jauja 1976 Coll 187P 542 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-45(P) 4438 B NW Jauja 1976 Coll 188P 543 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-46(P) 4439 D SW Jauja 1976 Coll 199P, 200P, 201P 489 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-47(P) 4438 D SE Jauja 1976 Coll 202P 488 (Box 54)
      - Jau-EI-48(P) 4438 B NE Jauja 1976 Coll 204P 495/545 (Box 54)